<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Mobile Mart</title>
    <subtitle>Mobiles and what else?</subtitle>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://indianmobilemart.com/" />
    <link rel="self" href="http://indianmobilemart.com/feed.xml" type="application/atom+xml" />
    <id>http://indianmobilemart.com/</id>
    <updated>2013-12-31T17:39:03Z</updated>
    
    <author>
        <name>indianmobilemart</name>
        <email>info@indianmobilemart.com</email>
        <uri>http://indianmobilemart.com/</uri>
    </author>
    
    
        <entry>
            <title>Review  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282</title>
            <link rel="alternate" href="http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/31/review-samsung-samsung-galaxy-star-duos-s5282/" type="text/html" />
            <id>http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/31/review-samsung-samsung-galaxy-star-duos-s5282/</id>
            <updated>2013-12-31T17:26:00Z</updated>
            
            
            <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Review  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 is the company&amp;#39;s take on Android, v4.1.2 (Jelly Bean) phones with 3 inches, 240 x 320 pixels inches screen. The handset giant is advertising the phone with many efforts. There&amp;#39;s also a major shift in terms of the build of the phone and in some other attributes.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will try to find in this review that whether this phone can make it in the top lead of Android, v4.1.2 (Jelly Bean) mobile phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Build/ Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When seen from far, it appear as a regular mobile phone, but a closer look proved it this new  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 is pretty well designed and slick phone.  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 has better design than Salora Salora POWERMaxx Z1 and Videocon Videocon V1654, and it even feels more compact. The phone has sexy rounded edges. It&amp;#39;s available in different colour variants which might feel good to some people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The front of the Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 features a 3 inches, 240 x 320 pixels 5-inch display and the earpiece,  , notification LED and the sensor array above it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul class=&#34;post_images inline-list&#34;&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/2852/n-1/samsung_galaxy_star_duos_s5282.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/2852/n-2/samsung_galaxy_star_duos_s5282.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/2852/n-4/samsung_galaxy_star_duos_s5282.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 features the Power / Screen lock key and the Volume rocker key at the right hand side, and two micro-SIM trays at the left side. The Micro-USB port sits at the top edge of the phone, while the 3.5mm headset jack is located at the bottom edge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The back of the  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 is dominated by a cover which is flanked by two plastic strips at the top and bottom. The Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 houses the 2 MP-megapixel camera lens that protrudes out a little,  and a big LED flash .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom strip houses the speaker grill of the phone. There&amp;#39;s some  branding at the middle of the Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 in the form of a logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the build quality of the  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 can be considered the best among all other  phones of similar range and category. The phone is well-built, exudes a feeling of durability and feels nice to hold. Despite sporting a 3 inches, 240 x 320 pixels-inch display, the phone is perfect for one-hand use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Display of  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 comes with a 3 inches, 240 x 320 pixels-inch display with pixels resolution and pixel density of ppi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The screen is one of the phone&amp;#39;s headline features, and thanks to that text and images looked crisp and sharp but we were not very impressed with the display&amp;#39;s colour reproduction, specially how it displayed blacks.  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282&amp;#39;s screen also looked a bit dull, and brightness levels were below par if you compare it with phones like the Salora Salora POWERMaxx Z1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Camera of  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 supports a 2 MP-megapixel rear camera .  offers its support for camera app that includes Normal,&lt;br&gt;
HDR, Smile detection, Panorama and Scene detection shot modes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our use, we found the camera of the  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 to be a bit off in terms of white balance and it softened the tone to a cooler shade. Images clicked with the phone&amp;#39;s rear camera lacked warmth and at times looked very bland. Images taken during the day were still passable but the ones taken in indoor light appeared totally different from the prevailing ambient light conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the cameras on the Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 are strictly average for a phone in this segment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Software/ User Interface of  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 runs Android, v4.1.2 (Jelly Bean), which is a very recent version of the OS and comes with some skinned elements of the UI like the app icons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#39;s custom UI layer is not as radical as HTC&amp;#39;s Sense UI or Samsung&amp;#39;s TouchWiz UI, but does add some customisation and third party apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the Salora Salora POWERMaxx Z1, the  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 also features some software tricks, including a new lock screen mechanism that allows the phone to be unlocked with a blow of air or if the phone is shaken. It works as promised but disables the lock screen widgets, so we just feel it&amp;#39;s too gimmicky. It&amp;#39;s not enabled by default.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Performance of  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 is powered by a 1 GHz Processor  1 GHz Processor processor with 512 MB  RAM onboard. There is  4 GB of internal storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Android, v4.1.2 (Jelly Bean), the overall experience of navigation through the interface was pleasant, thanks to the phone&amp;#39;s quad-core processor. We did not&lt;br&gt;
experience any lag while launching apps, playing games, scrolling web pages or switching between apps. It is safe to say that performance wise, the Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 scores well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 comes with a 1200 mAH, Li-ion Battery battery, and based on our experience, it will last you 320 hours. With medium to heavy usage, including 1-1.5 hours&lt;br&gt;
of phone calls, two e-mail accounts with push notifications, screen at maximum brightness, playing some music and video clips (about an hour), casual web&lt;br&gt;
browsing, Twitter notifications and WhatsApp chats, the phone lasted 840 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read detailed  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 review&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Display&lt;/strong&gt;  3 inches, 240 x 320 pixels-inch  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Processor&lt;/strong&gt;  1 GHz Processor  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Front Camera&lt;/strong&gt; 2 MP-megapixel  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAM&lt;/strong&gt; 512 MB  GB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OS&lt;/strong&gt;  Android, v4.1.2 (Jelly Bean)   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage&lt;/strong&gt; 4 GB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rear Camera&lt;/strong&gt; False  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery&lt;/strong&gt;  1200 mAH, Li-ion Battery  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;See full  Samsung Galaxy Star Duos S5282 specifications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
        </entry>
    
        <entry>
            <title>Review  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262</title>
            <link rel="alternate" href="http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/31/review-samsung-samsung-galaxy-star-pro-duos-s7262/" type="text/html" />
            <id>http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/31/review-samsung-samsung-galaxy-star-pro-duos-s7262/</id>
            <updated>2013-12-31T17:26:00Z</updated>
            
            
            <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Review  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 is the company&amp;#39;s take on Android, v4.1.2 phones with 4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels inches screen. The handset giant is advertising the phone with many efforts. There&amp;#39;s also a major shift in terms of the build of the phone and in some other attributes.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will try to find in this review that whether this phone can make it in the top lead of Android, v4.1.2 mobile phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Build/ Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When seen from far, it appear as a regular mobile phone, but a closer look proved it this new  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 is pretty well designed and slick phone.  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 has better design than Nokia Nokia Asha 201 and Micromax Micromax X368, and it even feels more compact. The phone has sexy rounded edges. It&amp;#39;s available in different colour variants which might feel good to some people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The front of the Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 features a 4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels 5-inch display and the earpiece,  , notification LED and the sensor array above it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul class=&#34;post_images inline-list&#34;&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/11013h9w9n6/n-2/samsung_galaxy_star_pro_duos_s7262.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/11013h9w9n6/n-1/samsung_galaxy_star_pro_duos_s7262.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/11013h9w9n6/n-4/samsung_galaxy_star_pro_duos_s7262.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 features the Power / Screen lock key and the Volume rocker key at the right hand side, and two micro-SIM trays at the left side. The Micro-USB port sits at the top edge of the phone, while the 3.5mm headset jack is located at the bottom edge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The back of the  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 is dominated by a cover which is flanked by two plastic strips at the top and bottom. The Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 houses the 2 MP-megapixel camera lens that protrudes out a little,  and a big LED flash .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom strip houses the speaker grill of the phone. There&amp;#39;s some  branding at the middle of the Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 in the form of a logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the build quality of the  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 can be considered the best among all other  phones of similar range and category. The phone is well-built, exudes a feeling of durability and feels nice to hold. Despite sporting a 4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels-inch display, the phone is perfect for one-hand use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Display of  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 comes with a 4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels-inch display with pixels resolution and pixel density of ppi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The screen is one of the phone&amp;#39;s headline features, and thanks to that text and images looked crisp and sharp but we were not very impressed with the display&amp;#39;s colour reproduction, specially how it displayed blacks.  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262&amp;#39;s screen also looked a bit dull, and brightness levels were below par if you compare it with phones like the Nokia Nokia Asha 201.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Camera of  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 supports a 2 MP-megapixel rear camera .  offers its support for camera app that includes Normal,&lt;br&gt;
HDR, Smile detection, Panorama and Scene detection shot modes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our use, we found the camera of the  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 to be a bit off in terms of white balance and it softened the tone to a cooler shade. Images clicked with the phone&amp;#39;s rear camera lacked warmth and at times looked very bland. Images taken during the day were still passable but the ones taken in indoor light appeared totally different from the prevailing ambient light conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the cameras on the Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 are strictly average for a phone in this segment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Software/ User Interface of  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 runs Android, v4.1.2, which is a very recent version of the OS and comes with some skinned elements of the UI like the app icons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#39;s custom UI layer is not as radical as HTC&amp;#39;s Sense UI or Samsung&amp;#39;s TouchWiz UI, but does add some customisation and third party apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the Nokia Nokia Asha 201, the  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 also features some software tricks, including a new lock screen mechanism that allows the phone to be unlocked with a blow of air or if the phone is shaken. It works as promised but disables the lock screen widgets, so we just feel it&amp;#39;s too gimmicky. It&amp;#39;s not enabled by default.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Performance of  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 is powered by a 1 GHz Processor  1 GHz Processor processor with 512 MB  RAM onboard. There is  4 GB of internal storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Android, v4.1.2, the overall experience of navigation through the interface was pleasant, thanks to the phone&amp;#39;s quad-core processor. We did not&lt;br&gt;
experience any lag while launching apps, playing games, scrolling web pages or switching between apps. It is safe to say that performance wise, the Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 scores well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 comes with a 1500 mAH, Li-ion Battery battery, and based on our experience, it will last you 370 hours. With medium to heavy usage, including 1-1.5 hours&lt;br&gt;
of phone calls, two e-mail accounts with push notifications, screen at maximum brightness, playing some music and video clips (about an hour), casual web&lt;br&gt;
browsing, Twitter notifications and WhatsApp chats, the phone lasted 900 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read detailed  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 review&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Display&lt;/strong&gt;  4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels-inch  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Processor&lt;/strong&gt;  1 GHz Processor  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Front Camera&lt;/strong&gt; 2 MP-megapixel  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAM&lt;/strong&gt; 512 MB  GB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OS&lt;/strong&gt;  Android, v4.1.2   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage&lt;/strong&gt; 4 GB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rear Camera&lt;/strong&gt; False  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery&lt;/strong&gt;  1500 mAH, Li-ion Battery  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;See full  Samsung Galaxy Star Pro Duos S7262 specifications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
        </entry>
    
        <entry>
            <title>Review  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562</title>
            <link rel="alternate" href="http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/31/review-samsung-samsung-galaxy-s-duos-s7562/" type="text/html" />
            <id>http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/31/review-samsung-samsung-galaxy-s-duos-s7562/</id>
            <updated>2013-12-31T17:13:00Z</updated>
            
            
            <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Review  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 is the company&amp;#39;s take on Android, v4.0 phones with 4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels inches screen. The handset giant is advertising the phone with many efforts. There&amp;#39;s also a major shift in terms of the build of the phone and in some other attributes.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will try to find in this review that whether this phone can make it in the top lead of Android, v4.0 mobile phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Build/ Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When seen from far, it appear as a regular mobile phone, but a closer look proved it this new  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 is pretty well designed and slick phone.  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 has better design than Fly Fly F451s and Micromax Micromax X456 Hook Up, and it even feels more compact. The phone has sexy rounded edges. It&amp;#39;s available in different colour variants which might feel good to some people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The front of the Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 features a 4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels 5-inch display and the earpiece,  and front camera  , notification LED and the sensor array above it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul class=&#34;post_images inline-list&#34;&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/2179/n-4/samsung_galaxy_s_duos_s7562.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/2179/n-1/samsung_galaxy_s_duos_s7562.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/2179/n-2/samsung_galaxy_s_duos_s7562.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 features the Power / Screen lock key and the Volume rocker key at the right hand side, and two micro-SIM trays at the left side. The Micro-USB port sits at the top edge of the phone, while the 3.5mm headset jack is located at the bottom edge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The back of the  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 is dominated by a cover which is flanked by two plastic strips at the top and bottom. The Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 houses the 5 MP with autofocus-megapixel camera lens that protrudes out a little,  and a big LED flash .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom strip houses the speaker grill of the phone. There&amp;#39;s some  branding at the middle of the Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 in the form of a logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the build quality of the  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 can be considered the best among all other  phones of similar range and category. The phone is well-built, exudes a feeling of durability and feels nice to hold. Despite sporting a 4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels-inch display, the phone is perfect for one-hand use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Display of  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 comes with a 4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels-inch display with pixels resolution and pixel density of ppi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The screen is one of the phone&amp;#39;s headline features, and thanks to that text and images looked crisp and sharp but we were not very impressed with the display&amp;#39;s colour reproduction, specially how it displayed blacks.  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562&amp;#39;s screen also looked a bit dull, and brightness levels were below par if you compare it with phones like the Fly Fly F451s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Camera of  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 supports a 5 MP with autofocus-megapixel rear camera  and a True-megapixel front facing camera.  offers its support for camera app that includes Normal,&lt;br&gt;
HDR, Smile detection, Panorama and Scene detection shot modes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our use, we found the camera of the  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 to be a bit off in terms of white balance and it softened the tone to a cooler shade. Images clicked with the phone&amp;#39;s rear camera lacked warmth and at times looked very bland. Images taken during the day were still passable but the ones taken in indoor light appeared totally different from the prevailing ambient light conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the cameras on the Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 are strictly average for a phone in this segment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Software/ User Interface of  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 runs Android, v4.0, which is a very recent version of the OS and comes with some skinned elements of the UI like the app icons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#39;s custom UI layer is not as radical as HTC&amp;#39;s Sense UI or Samsung&amp;#39;s TouchWiz UI, but does add some customisation and third party apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the Fly Fly F451s, the  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 also features some software tricks, including a new lock screen mechanism that allows the phone to be unlocked with a blow of air or if the phone is shaken. It works as promised but disables the lock screen widgets, so we just feel it&amp;#39;s too gimmicky. It&amp;#39;s not enabled by default.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Performance of  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 is powered by a 1 GHz Processor  1 GHz Processor processor with 768 MB  RAM onboard. There is  4 GB of internal storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Android, v4.0, the overall experience of navigation through the interface was pleasant, thanks to the phone&amp;#39;s quad-core processor. We did not&lt;br&gt;
experience any lag while launching apps, playing games, scrolling web pages or switching between apps. It is safe to say that performance wise, the Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 scores well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 comes with a 1500 mAH, Li-ion Battery battery, and based on our experience, it will last you 445 hours, 330 hours on 3G. With medium to heavy usage, including 1-1.5 hours&lt;br&gt;
of phone calls, two e-mail accounts with push notifications, screen at maximum brightness, playing some music and video clips (about an hour), casual web&lt;br&gt;
browsing, Twitter notifications and WhatsApp chats, the phone lasted 780 minutes, 445 minutes on 3G.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read detailed  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 review&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Display&lt;/strong&gt;  4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels-inch  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Processor&lt;/strong&gt;  1 GHz Processor  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Front Camera&lt;/strong&gt; 5 MP with autofocus-megapixel  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAM&lt;/strong&gt; 768 MB  GB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OS&lt;/strong&gt;  Android, v4.0   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage&lt;/strong&gt; 4 GB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rear Camera&lt;/strong&gt; True  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery&lt;/strong&gt;  1500 mAH, Li-ion Battery  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;See full  Samsung Galaxy S Duos S7562 specifications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
        </entry>
    
        <entry>
            <title>Review  Karbonn KT61 Iconik</title>
            <link rel="alternate" href="http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/31/review-karbonn-karbonn-kt61-iconik/" type="text/html" />
            <id>http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/31/review-karbonn-karbonn-kt61-iconik/</id>
            <updated>2013-12-31T15:36:00Z</updated>
            
            
            <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Review  Karbonn KT61 Iconik&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Karbonn KT61 Iconik Karbonn KT61 Iconik is the company&amp;#39;s take on Android, v2.1 phones with 2.8 inches inches screen. The handset giant is advertising the phone with many efforts. There&amp;#39;s also a major shift in terms of the build of the phone and in some other attributes.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will try to find in this review that whether this phone can make it in the top lead of Android, v2.1 mobile phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Build/ Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When seen from far, it appear as a regular mobile phone, but a closer look proved it this new  Karbonn KT61 Iconik is pretty well designed and slick phone.  Karbonn KT61 Iconik has better design than Intex Intex Aqua i7 and LG LG GX500, and it even feels more compact. The phone has sexy rounded edges. It&amp;#39;s available in different colour variants which might feel good to some people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The front of the Karbonn KT61 Iconik features a 2.8 inches 5-inch display and the earpiece,  , notification LED and the sensor array above it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul class=&#34;post_images inline-list&#34;&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Karbonn KT61 Iconik&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/2227/n-2/karbonn_kt61_iconik.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Karbonn KT61 Iconik&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/2227/n-1/karbonn_kt61_iconik.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Karbonn KT61 Iconik features the Power / Screen lock key and the Volume rocker key at the right hand side, and two micro-SIM trays at the left side. The Micro-USB port sits at the top edge of the phone, while the 3.5mm headset jack is located at the bottom edge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The back of the  Karbonn KT61 Iconik is dominated by a cover which is flanked by two plastic strips at the top and bottom. The Karbonn KT61 Iconik houses the 1.3 MP-megapixel camera lens that protrudes out a little,  and a big LED flash .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom strip houses the speaker grill of the phone. There&amp;#39;s some  branding at the middle of the Karbonn KT61 Iconik in the form of a logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the build quality of the  Karbonn KT61 Iconik can be considered the best among all other  phones of similar range and category. The phone is well-built, exudes a feeling of durability and feels nice to hold. Despite sporting a 2.8 inches-inch display, the phone is perfect for one-hand use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Display of  Karbonn KT61 Iconik&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Karbonn KT61 Iconik comes with a 2.8 inches-inch display with pixels resolution and pixel density of ppi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The screen is one of the phone&amp;#39;s headline features, and thanks to that text and images looked crisp and sharp but we were not very impressed with the display&amp;#39;s colour reproduction, specially how it displayed blacks.  Karbonn KT61 Iconik&amp;#39;s screen also looked a bit dull, and brightness levels were below par if you compare it with phones like the Intex Intex Aqua i7.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Camera of  Karbonn KT61 Iconik&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Karbonn KT61 Iconik supports a 1.3 MP-megapixel rear camera .  offers its support for camera app that includes Normal,&lt;br&gt;
HDR, Smile detection, Panorama and Scene detection shot modes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our use, we found the camera of the  Karbonn KT61 Iconik to be a bit off in terms of white balance and it softened the tone to a cooler shade. Images clicked with the phone&amp;#39;s rear camera lacked warmth and at times looked very bland. Images taken during the day were still passable but the ones taken in indoor light appeared totally different from the prevailing ambient light conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the cameras on the Karbonn KT61 Iconik are strictly average for a phone in this segment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Software/ User Interface of  Karbonn KT61 Iconik&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Karbonn KT61 Iconik runs Android, v2.1, which is a very recent version of the OS and comes with some skinned elements of the UI like the app icons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#39;s custom UI layer is not as radical as HTC&amp;#39;s Sense UI or Samsung&amp;#39;s TouchWiz UI, but does add some customisation and third party apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the Intex Intex Aqua i7, the  Karbonn KT61 Iconik also features some software tricks, including a new lock screen mechanism that allows the phone to be unlocked with a blow of air or if the phone is shaken. It works as promised but disables the lock screen widgets, so we just feel it&amp;#39;s too gimmicky. It&amp;#39;s not enabled by default.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Performance of  Karbonn KT61 Iconik&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Karbonn KT61 Iconik is powered by a 600 MHz Processor  600 MHz Processor processor with 512 MB  RAM onboard. There is  32 MB of internal storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Android, v2.1, the overall experience of navigation through the interface was pleasant, thanks to the phone&amp;#39;s quad-core processor. We did not&lt;br&gt;
experience any lag while launching apps, playing games, scrolling web pages or switching between apps. It is safe to say that performance wise, the Karbonn KT61 Iconik scores well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The  Karbonn KT61 Iconik comes with a 1000 mAH, Li-ion Battery battery, and based on our experience, it will last you 720 hours. With medium to heavy usage, including 1-1.5 hours&lt;br&gt;
of phone calls, two e-mail accounts with push notifications, screen at maximum brightness, playing some music and video clips (about an hour), casual web&lt;br&gt;
browsing, Twitter notifications and WhatsApp chats, the phone lasted 1020 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read detailed  Karbonn KT61 Iconik review&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Display&lt;/strong&gt;  2.8 inches-inch  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Processor&lt;/strong&gt;  600 MHz Processor  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Front Camera&lt;/strong&gt; 1.3 MP-megapixel  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAM&lt;/strong&gt; 512 MB  GB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OS&lt;/strong&gt;  Android, v2.1   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage&lt;/strong&gt; 32 MB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rear Camera&lt;/strong&gt; False  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery&lt;/strong&gt;  1000 mAH, Li-ion Battery  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;See full  Karbonn KT61 Iconik specifications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
        </entry>
    
        <entry>
            <title>Review  Acer Ferrari Liquid E</title>
            <link rel="alternate" href="http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/31/review-acer-acer-ferrari-liquid-e/" type="text/html" />
            <id>http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/31/review-acer-acer-ferrari-liquid-e/</id>
            <updated>2013-12-31T07:45:00Z</updated>
            
            
            <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Review  Acer Ferrari Liquid E&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Acer Ferrari Liquid E Acer Ferrari Liquid E is the company&amp;#39;s take on Android, v2.1 phones with 3.5 inches, 480 x 800 pixels inches screen. The handset giant is advertising the phone with many efforts. There&amp;#39;s also a major shift in terms of the build of the phone and in some other attributes.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will try to find in this review that whether this phone can make it in the top lead of Android, v2.1 mobile phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Build/ Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When seen from far, it appear as a regular mobile phone, but a closer look proved it this new  Acer Ferrari Liquid E is pretty well designed and slick phone.  Acer Ferrari Liquid E has better design than Zync Zync C18 and WickedLeak WickedLeak Wammy Sensation, and it even feels more compact. The phone has sexy rounded edges. It&amp;#39;s available in different colour variants which might feel good to some people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The front of the Acer Ferrari Liquid E features a 3.5 inches, 480 x 800 pixels 5-inch display and the earpiece,  , notification LED and the sensor array above it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul class=&#34;post_images inline-list&#34;&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Acer Ferrari Liquid E&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/387/n-1/acer_ferrari_liquid_e.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Acer Ferrari Liquid E&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/387/n-4/acer_ferrari_liquid_e.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Acer Ferrari Liquid E&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/387/n-2/acer_ferrari_liquid_e.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acer Ferrari Liquid E features the Power / Screen lock key and the Volume rocker key at the right hand side, and two micro-SIM trays at the left side. The Micro-USB port sits at the top edge of the phone, while the 3.5mm headset jack is located at the bottom edge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The back of the  Acer Ferrari Liquid E is dominated by a cover which is flanked by two plastic strips at the top and bottom. The Acer Ferrari Liquid E houses the 5 MP with autofocus-megapixel camera lens that protrudes out a little,  and a big LED flash .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom strip houses the speaker grill of the phone. There&amp;#39;s some  branding at the middle of the Acer Ferrari Liquid E in the form of a logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the build quality of the  Acer Ferrari Liquid E can be considered the best among all other  phones of similar range and category. The phone is well-built, exudes a feeling of durability and feels nice to hold. Despite sporting a 3.5 inches, 480 x 800 pixels-inch display, the phone is perfect for one-hand use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Display of  Acer Ferrari Liquid E&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Acer Ferrari Liquid E comes with a 3.5 inches, 480 x 800 pixels-inch display with pixels resolution and pixel density of ppi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The screen is one of the phone&amp;#39;s headline features, and thanks to that text and images looked crisp and sharp but we were not very impressed with the display&amp;#39;s colour reproduction, specially how it displayed blacks.  Acer Ferrari Liquid E&amp;#39;s screen also looked a bit dull, and brightness levels were below par if you compare it with phones like the Zync Zync C18.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Camera of  Acer Ferrari Liquid E&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Acer Ferrari Liquid E supports a 5 MP with autofocus-megapixel rear camera .  offers its support for camera app that includes Normal,&lt;br&gt;
HDR, Smile detection, Panorama and Scene detection shot modes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our use, we found the camera of the  Acer Ferrari Liquid E to be a bit off in terms of white balance and it softened the tone to a cooler shade. Images clicked with the phone&amp;#39;s rear camera lacked warmth and at times looked very bland. Images taken during the day were still passable but the ones taken in indoor light appeared totally different from the prevailing ambient light conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the cameras on the Acer Ferrari Liquid E are strictly average for a phone in this segment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Software/ User Interface of  Acer Ferrari Liquid E&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Acer Ferrari Liquid E runs Android, v2.1, which is a very recent version of the OS and comes with some skinned elements of the UI like the app icons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#39;s custom UI layer is not as radical as HTC&amp;#39;s Sense UI or Samsung&amp;#39;s TouchWiz UI, but does add some customisation and third party apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the Zync Zync C18, the  Acer Ferrari Liquid E also features some software tricks, including a new lock screen mechanism that allows the phone to be unlocked with a blow of air or if the phone is shaken. It works as promised but disables the lock screen widgets, so we just feel it&amp;#39;s too gimmicky. It&amp;#39;s not enabled by default.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Performance of  Acer Ferrari Liquid E&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Acer Ferrari Liquid E is powered by a Qualcomm 8250 Processor  768 MHz processor with 256 MB  RAM onboard. There is  512 MB of internal storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Android, v2.1, the overall experience of navigation through the interface was pleasant, thanks to the phone&amp;#39;s quad-core processor. We did not&lt;br&gt;
experience any lag while launching apps, playing games, scrolling web pages or switching between apps. It is safe to say that performance wise, the Acer Ferrari Liquid E scores well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The  Acer Ferrari Liquid E comes with a 1350 mAH, Li-ion Battery battery, and based on our experience, it will last you 400 hours. With medium to heavy usage, including 1-1.5 hours&lt;br&gt;
of phone calls, two e-mail accounts with push notifications, screen at maximum brightness, playing some music and video clips (about an hour), casual web&lt;br&gt;
browsing, Twitter notifications and WhatsApp chats, the phone lasted 300 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read detailed  Acer Ferrari Liquid E review&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Display&lt;/strong&gt;  3.5 inches, 480 x 800 pixels-inch  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Processor&lt;/strong&gt;  Qualcomm 8250 Processor  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Front Camera&lt;/strong&gt; 5 MP with autofocus-megapixel  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAM&lt;/strong&gt; 256 MB  GB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OS&lt;/strong&gt;  Android, v2.1   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage&lt;/strong&gt; 512 MB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rear Camera&lt;/strong&gt; False  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery&lt;/strong&gt;  1350 mAH, Li-ion Battery  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;See full  Acer Ferrari Liquid E specifications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
        </entry>
    
        <entry>
            <title>Review  Huawei Ascend G500</title>
            <link rel="alternate" href="http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/30/review-huawei-huawei-ascend-g500/" type="text/html" />
            <id>http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/30/review-huawei-huawei-ascend-g500/</id>
            <updated>2013-12-30T14:42:00Z</updated>
            
            
            <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Review  Huawei Ascend G500&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Huawei Ascend G500 Huawei Ascend G500 is the company&amp;#39;s take on Android, v4.0.4 phones with 4.3 inches, 540 x 960 pixels inches screen. The handset giant is advertising the phone with many efforts. There&amp;#39;s also a major shift in terms of the build of the phone and in some other attributes.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will try to find in this review that whether this phone can make it in the top lead of Android, v4.0.4 mobile phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Build/ Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When seen from far, it appear as a regular mobile phone, but a closer look proved it this new  Huawei Ascend G500 is pretty well designed and slick phone.  Huawei Ascend G500 has better design than Micromax Micromax X457 and Videocon Videocon Dost V1544, and it even feels more compact. The phone has sexy rounded edges. It&amp;#39;s available in different colour variants which might feel good to some people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The front of the Huawei Ascend G500 features a 4.3 inches, 540 x 960 pixels 5-inch display and the earpiece,  and front camera  , notification LED and the sensor array above it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul class=&#34;post_images inline-list&#34;&gt;


&lt;li&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Huawei Ascend G500&#34;] src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/2562/n-1/huawei_ascend_g500.jpg&#34;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Huawei Ascend G500 features the Power / Screen lock key and the Volume rocker key at the right hand side, and two micro-SIM trays at the left side. The Micro-USB port sits at the top edge of the phone, while the 3.5mm headset jack is located at the bottom edge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The back of the  Huawei Ascend G500 is dominated by a cover which is flanked by two plastic strips at the top and bottom. The Huawei Ascend G500 houses the 5 MP with autofocus-megapixel camera lens that protrudes out a little,  and a big LED flash .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom strip houses the speaker grill of the phone. There&amp;#39;s some  branding at the middle of the Huawei Ascend G500 in the form of a logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the build quality of the  Huawei Ascend G500 can be considered the best among all other  phones of similar range and category. The phone is well-built, exudes a feeling of durability and feels nice to hold. Despite sporting a 4.3 inches, 540 x 960 pixels-inch display, the phone is perfect for one-hand use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Display of  Huawei Ascend G500&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Huawei Ascend G500 comes with a 4.3 inches, 540 x 960 pixels-inch display with pixels resolution and pixel density of ppi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The screen is one of the phone&amp;#39;s headline features, and thanks to that text and images looked crisp and sharp but we were not very impressed with the display&amp;#39;s colour reproduction, specially how it displayed blacks.  Huawei Ascend G500&amp;#39;s screen also looked a bit dull, and brightness levels were below par if you compare it with phones like the Micromax Micromax X457.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Camera of  Huawei Ascend G500&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huawei Ascend G500 supports a 5 MP with autofocus-megapixel rear camera  and a True-megapixel front facing camera.  offers its support for camera app that includes Normal,&lt;br&gt;
HDR, Smile detection, Panorama and Scene detection shot modes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our use, we found the camera of the  Huawei Ascend G500 to be a bit off in terms of white balance and it softened the tone to a cooler shade. Images clicked with the phone&amp;#39;s rear camera lacked warmth and at times looked very bland. Images taken during the day were still passable but the ones taken in indoor light appeared totally different from the prevailing ambient light conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the cameras on the Huawei Ascend G500 are strictly average for a phone in this segment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Software/ User Interface of  Huawei Ascend G500&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huawei Ascend G500 runs Android, v4.0.4, which is a very recent version of the OS and comes with some skinned elements of the UI like the app icons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#39;s custom UI layer is not as radical as HTC&amp;#39;s Sense UI or Samsung&amp;#39;s TouchWiz UI, but does add some customisation and third party apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the Micromax Micromax X457, the  Huawei Ascend G500 also features some software tricks, including a new lock screen mechanism that allows the phone to be unlocked with a blow of air or if the phone is shaken. It works as promised but disables the lock screen widgets, so we just feel it&amp;#39;s too gimmicky. It&amp;#39;s not enabled by default.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Performance of  Huawei Ascend G500&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Huawei Ascend G500 is powered by a Dual Core Processor  1 GHz processor with 1 GB  RAM onboard. There is  4 GB of internal storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Android, v4.0.4, the overall experience of navigation through the interface was pleasant, thanks to the phone&amp;#39;s quad-core processor. We did not&lt;br&gt;
experience any lag while launching apps, playing games, scrolling web pages or switching between apps. It is safe to say that performance wise, the Huawei Ascend G500 scores well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The  Huawei Ascend G500 comes with a 1930 mAH, Li-ion Battery battery, and based on our experience, it will last you 450 hours. With medium to heavy usage, including 1-1.5 hours&lt;br&gt;
of phone calls, two e-mail accounts with push notifications, screen at maximum brightness, playing some music and video clips (about an hour), casual web&lt;br&gt;
browsing, Twitter notifications and WhatsApp chats, the phone lasted 300 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read detailed  Huawei Ascend G500 review&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Display&lt;/strong&gt;  4.3 inches, 540 x 960 pixels-inch  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Processor&lt;/strong&gt;  Dual Core Processor  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Front Camera&lt;/strong&gt; 5 MP with autofocus-megapixel  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAM&lt;/strong&gt; 1 GB  GB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OS&lt;/strong&gt;  Android, v4.0.4   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage&lt;/strong&gt; 4 GB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rear Camera&lt;/strong&gt; True  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery&lt;/strong&gt;  1930 mAH, Li-ion Battery  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;See full  Huawei Ascend G500 specifications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
        </entry>
    
</feed>