<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Mobile Mart</title>
    <subtitle>Mobiles and what else?</subtitle>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://indianmobilemart.com/" />
    <link rel="self" href="http://indianmobilemart.com/feed.xml" type="application/atom+xml" />
    <id>http://indianmobilemart.com/</id>
    <updated>2013-12-26T05:17:41Z</updated>
    
    <author>
        <name>indianmobilemart</name>
        <email>info@indianmobilemart.com</email>
        <uri>http://indianmobilemart.com/</uri>
    </author>
    
    
        <entry>
            <title>Review  Xolo A500s IPS</title>
            <link rel="alternate" href="http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/26/review-xolo-xolo-a500s-ips/" type="text/html" />
            <id>http://indianmobilemart.com/2013/12/26/review-xolo-xolo-a500s-ips/</id>
            <updated>2013-12-26T05:11:00Z</updated>
            
            
            <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Xolo A500s IPS review 2013&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Xolo A500s IPS Xolo A500s IPS is the company&amp;#39;s take on Android, v4.2 phones with 4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels inches screen. The handset giant is advertising the phone with many efforts. There&amp;#39;s also a major shift in terms of the build of the phone and in some other attributes.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will try to find in this review that whether this phone can make it in the top lead of Android, v4.2 mobile phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Build/ Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When seen from far, it appear as a regular mobile phone, but a closer look proved it this new  Xolo A500s IPS is pretty well designed and slick phone.  Xolo A500s IPS has better design than Micromax Micromax Canvas 4 (A210) and Motorola Motorola Moto G, and it even feels more compact. The phone has sexy rounded edges. It&amp;#39;s available in different colour variants which might feel good to some people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The front of the Xolo A500s IPS features a 4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels 5-inch display and the earpiece,  and front camera  , notification LED and the sensor array above it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/1101tck50va/n-1/xolo_a500s_ips.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Xolo A500s IPS&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/1101tck50va/n-4/xolo_a500s_ips.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Xolo A500s IPS&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;http://img.smartprix.com/mimg/1101tck50va/n-2/xolo_a500s_ips.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Xolo A500s IPS&#34;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xolo A500s IPS features the Power / Screen lock key and the Volume rocker key at the right hand side, and two micro-SIM trays at the left side. The Micro-USB port sits at the top edge of the phone, while the 3.5mm headset jack is located at the bottom edge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The back of the  Xolo A500s IPS is dominated by a cover which is flanked by two plastic strips at the top and bottom. The Xolo A500s IPS houses the 5 MP-megapixel camera lens that protrudes out a little,  and a big LED flash .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom strip houses the speaker grill of the phone. There&amp;#39;s some  branding at the middle of the Xolo A500s IPS in the form of a logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the build quality of the  Xolo A500s IPS can be considered the best among all other  phones of similar range and category. The phone is well-built, exudes a feeling of durability and feels nice to hold. Despite sporting a 4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels-inch display, the phone is perfect for one-hand use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Display of  Xolo A500s IPS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Xolo A500s IPS comes with a 4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels-inch display with pixels resolution and pixel density of ppi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The screen is one of the phone&amp;#39;s headline features, and thanks to that text and images looked crisp and sharp but we were not very impressed with the display&amp;#39;s colour reproduction, specially how it displayed blacks.  Xolo A500s IPS&amp;#39;s screen also looked a bit dull, and brightness levels were below par if you compare it with phones like the Micromax Micromax Canvas 4 (A210).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Camera of  Xolo A500s IPS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xolo A500s IPS supports a 5 MP-megapixel rear camera  and a True-megapixel front facing camera.  offers its support for camera app that includes Normal,&lt;br&gt;
HDR, Smile detection, Panorama and Scene detection shot modes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our use, we found the camera of the  Xolo A500s IPS to be a bit off in terms of white balance and it softened the tone to a cooler shade. Images clicked with the phone&amp;#39;s rear camera lacked warmth and at times looked very bland. Images taken during the day were still passable but the ones taken in indoor light appeared totally different from the prevailing ambient light conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the cameras on the Xolo A500s IPS are strictly average for a phone in this segment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Software/ User Interface of  Xolo A500s IPS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xolo A500s IPS runs Android, v4.2, which is a very recent version of the OS and comes with some skinned elements of the UI like the app icons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#39;s custom UI layer is not as radical as HTC&amp;#39;s Sense UI or Samsung&amp;#39;s TouchWiz UI, but does add some customisation and third party apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like the Micromax Micromax Canvas 4 (A210), the  Xolo A500s IPS also features some software tricks, including a new lock screen mechanism that allows the phone to be unlocked with a blow of air or if the phone is shaken. It works as promised but disables the lock screen widgets, so we just feel it&amp;#39;s too gimmicky. It&amp;#39;s not enabled by default.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Performance of  Xolo A500s IPS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Xolo A500s IPS is powered by a Dual Core Processor  1.3 GHz processor with 512 MB  RAM onboard. There is  4 GB of internal storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Android, v4.2, the overall experience of navigation through the interface was pleasant, thanks to the phone&amp;#39;s quad-core processor. We did not&lt;br&gt;
experience any lag while launching apps, playing games, scrolling web pages or switching between apps. It is safe to say that performance wise, the Xolo A500s IPS scores well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The  Xolo A500s IPS comes with a 1400 mAH, Li-ion Battery battery, and based on our experience, it will last you 520 hours, 577 hours on 3G. With medium to heavy usage, including 1-1.5 hours&lt;br&gt;
of phone calls, two e-mail accounts with push notifications, screen at maximum brightness, playing some music and video clips (about an hour), casual web&lt;br&gt;
browsing, Twitter notifications and WhatsApp chats, the phone lasted 1020 minutes, 720 minutes on 3G.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read detailed  Xolo A500s IPS review&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Display&lt;/strong&gt;  4 inches, 480 x 800 pixels-inch  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Processor&lt;/strong&gt;  Dual Core Processor  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Front Camera&lt;/strong&gt; 5 MP-megapixel  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAM&lt;/strong&gt; 512 MB  GB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OS&lt;/strong&gt;  Android, v4.2   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage&lt;/strong&gt; 4 GB  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rear Camera&lt;/strong&gt; True  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery&lt;/strong&gt;  1400 mAH, Li-ion Battery  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;&#34;&gt;See full  Xolo A500s IPS specifications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
        </entry>
    
</feed>